Guide to the Carole De Saram Papers 1972-2011 MS 3059
New-York Historical Society
- Series 2: Publications, 1974-2009; 1 Linear feet
  - The New York State Legislative Process: An Evaluation and Blueprint for Reform by Jeremy M. Creelan & Laura M. Moulton. Executive Summary, Brennan Center for Justice at NYU School of Law., 2004 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 7)
  - New St. John's Park: Born Of Need, Tempered by Life: The Rebirth of Hudson Square, 1866-2009 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    Community plan in response to the New York Department of Sanitation plan for Hudson Square.
  - PlaNYC: A Greener, Greater New York. Produced by The City of New York, Mayor Michael R. Bloomberg, circa 2007 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 7)
  - Prologue: Journal of the National Archives, 1981 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 7)
    Includes: Vol 13 No 1 Spring 1981, Vol 13 No 2 Summer 1981
  - Prologue: Journal of the National Archives, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 8)
    Includes: Vol 14 No 3 Fall 1982, Vol 14 No 4 Winter 1982, Vol 15 No 1 Spring 1983, Vol 15 No 2 Summer 1983, Vol 15 No 3 Fall 1983, Vol 15 No 4 Winter 1983
  - Prologue: Journal of the National Archives, 1984 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 9)
    Includes: Vol 16 No 2 Summer 1984
  - Village Views published by The Society for the Architecture of the City, Inc., 1986-1989 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 9)
    Includes: Vol III Num 3, Vol V Num 1, Vol V Num 4.
  - Zoned Out: A Call to Overhaul New York's Zoning Laws, 2000, 2005 (Box over-size small)
    Includes booklet by the Municipal Art Society of New York, the transmittal letter of the booklet to de Saram, and a 2005 donation request letter.
  - Pamphlets, Guides, and Ephemera related to Tribeca, 1983-2000 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 10)
  - Pamphlets, Guides, and Ephemera related to NYC Landmarks, 1989-2005 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 11)
  - Pamphlets, Guides, and Ephemera related to NYC in general, 1977-2002 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 12)